

Yasser Hussien

Date of birth: 19/01/1998

Nationality: Syrian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Arab Maghreb Street ,Lattakia,Syria, null Lattakia, Syria

yasserhussien162@gmail.co m

(+963) 947569492

ABOUT MF

I have good Knowledge in analysis and unit Tests using Scala language, two years experience in the field of Android applications and I have the ability to learn new programming languages or to deal with specific software libraries and basic knowledge in Flutter.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/01/2022 - CURRENT

SCASE Company

Software Engineer

Analysis and Testing using Scala language

16/01/2021 - 27/09/2021 - Lattakia, Syria

TEC /Time Engineering Company

Android Developer

Programming Android application

01/10/2020 - CURRENT - Lattakia, Syria

Infinity Centre

I have started training some students in the field of programming Android applications in infinity centre

10/04/2017 - 2018

ACM TishreenCPC / Contestant

I am a Contestant at Tishreen Colligate Programming Contest working on problems with two other persons for five hours

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2015 - 2021

I study informatics engineering at Tishreen University

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Arabic

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
B1	B1	production	interaction	B1
		B1	B1	

DIGITAL SKILLS

SCALA / Flutter Dart / GIT (GitHub) / Agile (Scrum) / MySQL / Unit Testing / C++ / Java / Design Patterns, SOLID design

PROJECTS

Pharma Time application

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.timeengcom.timepharmacy

This program allows users to access all the information of Syrian and imported medicines without the need to connect to the Internet, with pictures of medicines, presentation of educational courses and comprehensive questions in the field of medicine.

Graduation Project

An application that helps people to search for the nearest hospital using Google Maps and search for blood bags and oxygen cylinders, and the user can add himself as a donor.

The application also encrypts user data via QR Code and can print it in the form of a necklace

Mobile language used: Java

Backend language: php Database used: MySql

Firebase notification service has been used

Blood Bank application

https://drive.google.com/file/d/

14Q0HQo0afFwJkfkTsArqd6Rg2mS7E31_/view?usp=sharing

This project allows the user to search for the appropriate blood group in the blood bank, and in the event that there is no presence, a notification is sent to all users that there is a case in need of blood transfusion, and an announcement is published within the application(has been used Firebase Notification to send notification to users)

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Fast Learner
- Ambitious
- Team Player
- Patient